youronlinechoices.com 2010-09-29

# Privacy | Your Online Choices - a guide to online behavioural advertising and online privacy

**We are committed to upholding your privacy as a valued user of this website.**

This website is run by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB). The personal data we collect, process or use is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy, described below. Whenever you give us personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this policy, including our use of cookies explained below.

**Your data**

We log your Internet Protocol (IP) address and use cookies to recognise you when you return to our site.

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a text-only string of data that is entered into the cookie file or “memory” of the browser on your computer. It will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

**How to manage the use of cookies at our website**

All browser technologies enable you to manage the cookies in the cookie folder of your browser. This means that you can either delete cookies from your cookie folder once you have finished your visit at our site or you can set your preferences with regard to the use of cookies before you begin surfing our website. Please note that deleting or rejecting cookies may affect your user experience of our website for example you may be asked to re-enter some information e.g. your name and password to use some pages.

**How we use cookies**

Using cookies is useful for us in optimising our site and making sure we are offering the best content to our users. We use cookies in order to give us information on the number of visitors to different parts of our website and thus to monitor which areas are most useful. We do not use them to identify you.

**How we use your personal data**

We collect your personal data if you choose to make a complaint about one of the companies complying with the Good Practice Principles for behavioural advertising. In some cases we will need to pass this personal information to the relevant company concerned to help address the complaint.  We also collect your personal data if you seek feedback via email using the ‘feedback’ function on this website.

**Links**

This site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of any of these sites.

**Access to your personal data**

We endeavour to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. If you become aware of any errors or if you would like to see what personal data we have collected from you, please e-mail [info@iabuk.net](mailto:info@iabuk.net "mailto:info@iabuk.net Email IAB").

**Changes to this policy**

This privacy policy may change at any time, so you may wish to check it each time you visit our website.
